http://www.astrophotography.com.au/about/privacy-policy/

Personal information provided during the purchasing of any products from Astro Photography Australia will only be used for the purpose of that purchase except where required by law.
Under no circumstances will your personal information be sold by Astro Photography Australia to any third party.
To protect your personal information during an online transaction Astro Photography Australia makes use of the online purchasing gateway PayPal who provides secure online payment facilities, external to our web site.
Personal information provided for newsletter subscriptions will only ever be used for the sending of the Astro Photography Australia newsletter and never any other purpose. This newsletter may include some specials specific to the Astro Photography Australia web site in addition to general news articles.
If you have any questions about privacy issues relating to Astro Photography Australia please contact us at info@astrophotography.com.au.
Any changes to this privacy policy will be made available at this page.
Remote telescope and observatory hosting in the dark skies of the Central Wheatbelt, Western Australia.
Shopping CartSign up for Astro Photography Australia Updates by email
Email Address*
First Name
Last Name
* = required field
Customers
Preferred Format
HTML
Text
powered by MailChimp!
Find astrophotography by clicking a tag belowairglow
alpha centauri
astrophotography
Barnard's Loop
cloud
coffee mug
comet
constellation
wheatbelt
Search for:
About Started by Roger Groom in 2003 Astro Photography Australia sells prints, copyright use, acrylic photo blocks and mugs of astrophotography. Every print is high quality made to last, making great gifts.
Stock Availability Stock quantities are shown for products, I attempt to keep these as up to date. Many 5x7, 12x8 and 50x33 prints are in stock all the time and ship within two business days. I tend to produce larger prints on-demand requiring a lead time of one to two weeks. Astro Mugs and Acrylic Photo Blocks stock quantities on the website are accurate, those not in stock require a two week lead time. If timing is critical for your order please contact me first to check stock on hand.
Recent Posts
Road-tripping for astronomy
Leofoto Tripod Review – Ranger LS-284CVL
Deep Sky images abound!
